http://www.rowenta.com/legal-terms

Password lost
You have lost your password. Please enter your email address and we will send you a password
Legal Terms
This website (the “Website”) editor is: SEB DEVELOPPEMENT, a Société par Actions Simplifiées under French law with a share capital of 3,000,000 Euros having its registered office at 4 Chemin du Petit Bois, 69130 ECULLY, registered under the under number B 016 950 842 RCS Lyon - Tel 0033 4 72 18 18 18 Fax 0033 4 72 18 16 55 The chief editor (“Directeur de publication”) of the Website is: Gilles PELISSIER The hosting provider of the Website is: EOLAS, a Société à Responsabilité Limitée under French law with a share capital of 228,988 euros having its registered office at 29 rue Sevran, 38000 GRENOBLE, registered under the number B 382 198 794 RCS Grenoble – Tel 04 76 44 50 50 Fax 04 76 44 00 41 General information about this website: This website is owned by SEB DEVELOPPEMENT, which is headquartered in BP 172, 69134 Ecully cedex, France. SEB DEVELOPPEMENT is part of the Groupe SEB. Groupe SEB means all affiliated directly or indirectly to SEB SA , 4 M, Chemin du Petit Bois, Cedex 69132 ECULLY companies - Tel. 04 72 18 18 18 , Fax 04 72 18 16 55 Terms of use
1. Preamble
Before accessing the website, please carefully read carefully these Terms of Use describing the	general contractual terms applicable to the use of the Website accessible at Legal terms.
2. Acceptance of Terms of Use
By accessing and / or using this Website, you confirm that you accept these Terms of Use and all terms and conditions contained or to which reference is made.If you deny all or part of any obligations or the Terms of Use or conditions contained herein, please do not use the Website.
3. Modification of the Website and Terms of Use
We may change at any time, without notice, all or part of the Website and / or these Terms of Use. You must read and regularly check the Terms of Use and any conditions to which reference is made		in order to remain constantly informed of the terms that apply to you.The use of the website following changes to these Terms of Use or to the Website constitutes acceptance of the modifications.
4. Intellectual Property
You expressly acknowledge that we have the exclusive ownership of all components of the website	including, but not limited to, text, photographs, illustrations , video, audio, design, appearance, structure, concepts, trademarks, logos, technical and graphic solutions, databases, software, source code available on the Website and / or transiting through the Website.Any reproduction, presentation, adaptation, modification, publication, transmission, alteration, incorporation into another web website, commercial use and/or total or partial reuse of the Website or any of its elements, by any means whatsoever and on any medium whatsoever, is strictly prohibited.Any unauthorized use of the Website or its contents, information disclosed therein engages the liability of the user and constitutes an infringement punished under articles L. 335-2 of the French Intellectual Property Code.The same prohibition applies for databases, if any, present on the Website which are protected by the provisions of Articles L. 341-1 and following of the French Intellectual Property Code. As such,	any reproduction or retrieval engages the responsibility of the user.This article cannot be regarded as limiting any other cause of action against the responsible for unauthorized use of the Website or its content.
5. Liability and Website Access
All data, information and publications accessible or downloaded from the Website are provided for informational purposes and are in no way exhaustive. We will not guarantee the accuracy, completeness or timeliness of information available on the website. The information on this
website may contain technical inaccuracies and / or typographical errors. This information may be periodically modified and the changes will be incorporated into new versions.We cannot guarantee that the Website is free of defects, errors or bugs, or that they may be corrected, or that the Website will operate without interruption or failure, or that it is compatible	with any type of equipment.You acknowledge having the skills and resources and knowledge necessary to use the Website. You acknowledge also be fully responsible for the conservation and security of the integrity of your data, your hardware and software when you access the Website.We or any of the companies affiliated to the GROUPE SEB will not be liable for any direct or indirect damages resulting from use of the Website, the content of the Website or any other element present on hosting servers of the website.We reserve the right to modify, terminate, suspend or discontinue at any time and without notice, for any reason and in our sole discretion, access to all or part of the Website, including without limitation, the content,functionality and availability hours. Our liability shall in no event be sought in case of unavailability of the Website.For your comments and suggestions on the website, please contact the webmaster.
6. Confidentiality
Personal data provided or collected through the Website are used only in accordance with our	privacy policy and the present Terms of Use and are subject to the Privacy Policy posted on the Website.
7. Links to other websites
The website provides access to other websites via hyperlinks. We are not manager of these sites and cannot control their content. Accordingly, we cannot in any way be held liable for the content of these websites, nor for any collection and transmission of personal data, installation of cookies or any other similar process, made
8. Data Protection
The information collected on the Website is subject to a data processing by the company SEB DEVELOPPEMENT, the data controller. Pursuant to the French Data Protection Act ("Loi Informatique et Libertés") n° 78-17 of 6 January 1978 as amended by Law No. 2004-801 of 6 August 2004, the website has been declared to the French Data Protection Authority (CNIL).Any person whose data are collected and processed on the Website has a right of access, correction and deletion of any personal data relating to him/her as well as a right to object upon legitimate grounds to the processing of his/her data. To exercise these rights you can contact us by writing the following address:SERVICE CONSOMMATEURS ROWENTATSA 9200269134 Ecully CedexTél. 09 74 50 47 74Fax 04 37 59 10 20You can also contact the customer service
9. Credits
Website design, creation, coordination & content production : wax-interactive.com
Loading...
Compare
